3dprinting.org 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy | 3DPrinting.org

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to 3DPrinting.org: Where 3D People Connect and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to 3DPrinting.org: Where 3D People Connect include 3DPrinting.org. The 3DPrinting.org website is a Forum and Community site. By using the 3DPrinting.org website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by 3DPrinting.org. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the 3DPrinting.org website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through 3DPrinting.org's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

3DPrinting.org encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from 3DPrinting.org so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. 3DPrinting.org is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the 3DPrinting.org website.

#### Use of Cookies

The 3DPrinting.org website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize 3DPrinting.org pages, or register with 3DPrinting.org site or services, a cookie helps 3DPrinting.org to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same 3DPrinting.org website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the 3DPrinting.org features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the 3DPrinting.org services or websites you visit.

#### Security of your Personal Information

3DPrinting.org uses standard means to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

PayPal processes all financial transactions. No credit card data is processed or stored on 3DPrinting.org.

#### Children Under Thirteen

3DPrinting.org does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from 3DPrinting.org by contacting us here:

Email: support@3dprinting.org

#### Changes to this Statement

3DPrinting.org will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. 3DPrinting.org encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how 3DPrinting.org is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

3DPrinting.org welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that 3DPrinting.org has not adhered to this Statement, please contact 3DPrinting.org at:

3DPrinting.org: Where 3D People Connect  
14158H Willard Rd  
Chantilly, Virginia 20151

Email Address:  
support@3dprinting.org

Effective as of May 01, 2014
